financialsecrets.info 2005-05-26

# index

**PRIVACY NOTICE**

What kind of personal information Financialsecrets.info collects and how it is collected  
Financialsecrets.info collects personal information from a variety of sources, including from members of the public, advertisers, prospective employees, mailing lists, recruitment agencies, contractors and business partners.

In general, the personal information Financialsecrets.info collects includes (but is not limited to) name, address, contact details, gender, occupation, in some cases membership of professional associations and, where relevant, financial information, including credit card information, banking details and income information.

Personal Information you provide: We store the personal information you enter on the Financialsecrets.info Network or give to Financialsecrets.info in other ways. We obtain most personal information through the Financialsecrets.info Network membership registration process and updates to membership details. You may provide information when you request or acquire a product or service from Financialsecrets.info or its related companies, provide a product or service to Financialsecrets.info , complete a survey or questionnaire, enter a competition, participate in forums or when you communicate with Financialsecrets.info by e-mail, telephone or in writing (for example if you contact customer service or provide feedback).

Automatic collection: Cookies: We may use a feature of your browser called a cookie to assign your computer a 'User ID'. Cookies do not contain information by which Financialsecrets.info can identify you. They identify your computer to our servers. You may configure your browser so that you are notified before a cookie is downloaded or so that your browser does not accept cookies. Financialsecrets.info may use information contained in cookies to make assumptions about the user of the computer and to provide users of that computer with focused advertising which Financialsecrets.info believes may be of interest, based on that information. To disable your cookies, please refer to the help menu within your Internet browser.

Indirect collection: Financialsecrets.info endeavours to collect personal information about an individual only from that individual. In some circumstances Financialsecrets.info may obtain personal information from a third party. If you provide personal information about another person to Financialsecrets.info , Financialsecrets.info requires that you inform that person you have done so and provide them with a copy of this policy.

How Financialsecrets.info uses the information you provide  
Financialsecrets.info may use information it collects from you for the primary purpose for which it is collected and for such other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose of collection.

Financialsecrets.info generally uses personal information to:

    * provide you with products or services you have requested  
    * personalise and customise your experiences on the Financialsecrets.info Network;  
    * help Financialsecrets.info manage and enhance its services;  
    * communicate with you;  
    * provide you with ongoing information about opportunities on the Financialsecrets.info Network in which Financialsecrets.info believes you may be interested;  
    * give you the opportunity from time to time to receive e-mail and 'e-newsletters' from Financialsecrets.info .

In most cases where Financialsecrets.info asks you to provide information about yourself, if you do not provide Financialsecrets.info with that information, Financialsecrets.info will not be able to provide you with the requested product or service.

Financialsecrets.info may also provide your information to:

    * third parties engaged by Financialsecrets.info to perform functions on its behalf, such as processing credit card information, mailouts, debt collection, marketing, research and advertising;

If Financialsecrets.info sells part of its business, personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the purchaser.

The Financialsecrets.info Network contains features where you are invited to send personal information to organisations other than Financialsecrets.info . The choice to send such information to these organisations is entirely yours. You should be aware that any such information you choose to send will not be bound by this policy.

How Financialsecrets.info treats sensitive information  
"Sensitive Information" means information relating to a person's racial or ethnic origin, membership of political bodies, religion, membership of a trade union or professional or trade association, sexual preferences, criminal record and health.

Financialsecrets.info may use and disclose Sensitive Information only for the purpose for which it was provided or a directly related secondary purpose or as allowed by law unless you have agreed otherwise.

Management and security of personal information  
Financialsecrets.info has appointed a Privacy Officer to oversee Financialsecrets.info 's management of personal information in accordance with this policy and the Commonwealth Privacy Act.

Financialsecrets.info protects the personal information Financialsecrets.info holds from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure by various means including firewalls, pass word access, secure servers and encryption of credit card transactions.

Updating personal information  
Financialsecrets.info endeavours to ensure that the personal information it holds is accurate, complete and up-to-date. You can update your Financialsecrets.info membership information via the 'Update your details' section on any of the sites within the Financialsecrets.info Network.

Seeking access to the personal information Financialsecrets.info holds about you  
You have the right to seek access the personal information held about you and to advise Financialsecrets.info of any inaccuracy. There are some exceptions to this right set out in the Privacy Act.

If you make an access request, Financialsecrets.info will ask you to verify your identity and specify what information you require. Financialsecrets.info may charge a fee to cover the costs of meeting your request.

Membership information: Financialsecrets.info Network Members can access the membership information Financialsecrets.info holds about them at any time via the 'Update your details' section on any of the sites within the Financialsecrets.info Network.

How to contact Financialsecrets.info  
If you have enquiries or wish to provide feedback about this policy, please e-mail info@Financialsecrets.info
